<resources>
    <string name="app_name">State Capitals\nQuiz</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="quiz_purpose">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3>What does this app do?</h3>\n\nThis is a quiz application that allows a user to test their knowledge on the capitals of the 50 states in the US.
            The quiz is composed of 6 randomly selected questions each asking the user to identify a given state’s capital with 3 possible answer choices (only one correct answer).
            The app will record correct and incorrect questions as the user swipes left to the next question. Once, the user has answered the last question and swiped-left,
            the last screen will be displayed showing the result of the current quiz to the user.
            From this point, the app will store the date and time of the quiz and its result, so it can be saved under the ”Past Quizzes” section.
        ]]>
	</string>

    <string name="how_to_use">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3>How to use the app?</h3> \n\n Use the navigation drawer which will present the user with a variety of options to navigate to different screens that include
            starting a “New Quiz,” looking at “Past Quizzes,” and a “Help Menu”. When the user is taking a quiz, the user can select an answer by pressing on one
            of the radio buttons, and the user can go to the next question by swiping left. The “current quiz results” screen is accessed when the final left-swipe
            is made when the user is on the last question. The user can access the “Past Quizzes” screen via navigation drawer or from the “current quiz results” screen.
            On the “Past Quizzes” screen, it displays a list of all the past quizzes taken ordered by date/time from newest to oldest.
        ]]>
	</string>
</resources>